Guide to the Casey Recordings, 1944-1985 CASEY.2001
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Classical, 1945-1948, 1962, 1965, 1967, 1971-1973, 1975, 1980; II.
  - Chausson Concerto for Violin, Piano & String Quartet, Op. 21 (Record CAS CLA 0028)
    This album consists of 4 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes First movement (Part 1). Side (B) includes Fourth movement: Finale (conc.).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes First movement (Part 2). Side (B) includes Fourth movement: Finale (Part 1).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes First movement (conc.). Side (B) includes Third movement: Grave (conc.).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes Second movement: Sicilienne. Side (B) includes Third movement: Grave (Part 1). Album also includes program notes by Veinus, A. included in booklet.
  - Fantaisie-Impromptu in C-Sharp Minor, Posthumous, Op. 66; Nocturne in E-Flat, Op. 9, No. 2 (Record CAS CLA 0029)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Fantaisie-Impromptu in C-Sharp Minor, Posthumous, Op. 66. Side (B) includes Nocturne in E-Flat, Op. 9, No. 2. The original sleeve is in new sleeve.
  - Organ Recital: Charles M. Courboin, organist, from St. Patrick's Cathedral, New York (Record CAS CLA 0030)
    This album consists of 3 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes Ave Verum. Side (B) includes (A) Jesus, My Lord (B) Holy God, We Praise Thy Name.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes Ave Maria. Side (B) includes Adoration (based on the Gregorian "Ave Maria).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes Silent Night. Side (B) includes (A) O Lord, I am Not Worthy (B) Hail, Glorious St. Patrick. This album includes notes inside cover.
  - Debussy Quartet in G Minor, Op. 10 (Record CAS CLA 0031)
    This album consists of 4 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes I. Animé et trè décidé (Part 1). Side (B) includes IV. Finale: Vivace.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes I. Animé et très décidé (conc.). Side (B) includes IV. Très modéré (conc.).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes II. Assez vif e bien rhythme. Side (B) includes IV. Très modéré (Part 1).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes III. Andantino doucement expressif (Part 1). Side (B) includes III. Andantino doucement expressif (conc.). This album also includes program notes inside cover.
  - Mattia Battistini sings A tanto Amero from Donizetti's opera La Favorita and Il mio lionello from von Flotow's opera Martha, 1947 (Record CAS CLA 0032)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes A tanto amor. Side (B) includes Il mio lionello. Album is in gold cover. Recorded in 1907.
  - La Favorita-Anathème de Balthazar; Le Châlet-Chanson Militaire, 1946 (Record CAS CLA 0034)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes La Favorita-Anathème de Balthazar. Side (B) includes Le Châlet-Chanson Militaire. Original sleeve is in new sleeve.
  - La Favorita: Act III (Record CAS CLA 0035)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes O Mio Fernando (Part 1). Side (B) includes O Mio Fernando (conc.).
  - Werrenrath, Reinald (baritone) with orchestra; The Palms; The Lost Chord (Record CAS CLA 0035.1)
    This album consists of 1 dsic with 2 sides. Side (A) includes The Palms. Side (B) includes The Lost Chord.
  - A Program of Music by César Franck: Psyché and Le Chasseur Maudit (Record CAS CLA 0036)
    This album consists of 4 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes I. Sommeil de Psyché (Part 1). Side (B) includes Le Chasseur Maudit (Symphonic Poem) (conc.).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes (A) I. Sommeil de Psyché (Part 1) (conc.) (B) II. Psyché enlevée par les Zéphyrs. Side (B) includes Le Chasseur Maudit (Symphonic Poem) (Part 3).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes III. Psyché et Eros (Part 1). Side (B) includes Le Chasseur Maudit (Symphonic Poem) (Part 2).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes III. Psyché et Eros (conc.). Side (B) includes Le Chasseur Maudit (Symphonic Poem) (Part 1). The album also includes a brief introductory note.
  - Franck Sonata in A Major (Record CAS CLA 0037)
    This album consists of 3 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes I: Allegro ben moderato (Part 1). Side (B) includes IV: Allegretto poco mosso (conc.).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes (A) I: Allegro ben moderato (conc.) (B) II: Allegro. Side (B) includes (A) III:Recitativo-Fantasia (conc.) (B) IV: Allegretto poco mosso (Part 1).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes II: Allegro (conc.). Side (B) includes III:Recitativo-Fantasia (Part 1). Album also includes program notes inside album cover.
  - Heifetz, Jascha (violin) with Bay, Emmanuel (piano); Alt Wien; Valse Bluette (Record CAS CLA 0038)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Alt Wien. Side (B) includes Valse Bluette.
  - Ancona, Mario (baritone) with orchestra; Faust: Act II; The Masked Ball: Act III (Record CAS CLA 0039)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Dio possente. Side (B) includes Er tu che macchiavi quell'anima.
  - Charles Dalmores sings Ah! leve-toi soleil from Gounod's opera Romeo et Juliette and La fluer que tu m'avais jetée from Bizet's opera Carmen, 1947 (Record CAS CLA 0040)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Ah! leve-toi soleil. Side (B) includes La fleur que tu m'avais jetées. The album is in a gold cover. Recorded in 1912.
  - Caruso, Enrico (tenor) with orchestra; La Juive: Act IV; Manon Lescaut: Act III (Record CAS CLA 0041)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Rachel, quand du Seigneur la grâce tutélaire. Side (B) includes (A) Recitative: Je suis seul (B) Aria: Ah! fuyez dolce image.
  - The Messiah (Record CAS CLA 0042)
    This album consists of 11 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes Introductory Talk (Beecham). Side (B) includes Surely He Hath Borne Our Griefs.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes Overture. Side (B) includes He Was Despised (conc.).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes Comfort Ye, My People. Side (B) includes He Was Despised (Part 1).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes Ev'ry Valley Shall Be Exalted. Side (B) includes Behold the Lamb of God.
    Disc 5 side (A) includes And the Glory of the Lord. Side (B) includes His Yoke is Easy.
    Disc 6 side (A) includes (A) Thus Saith the Lord (B) But Who May Abide (Part 1). Side (B) includes He Shall Feed His Flocks (Come Unto Him)(conc.).
    Disc 7 side (A) includes (A) But Who Shall Abide (B) And He Shall Purify. Side (B) includes (A) Then Shall the Eyes (B) He Shall Feed His Flocks (Part 1).
    Disc 8 side (A) includes (A) Behold, a Virgin Shalle Conceive (B) O Thou That Tellest (Part 1). Side (B) includes Rejoice Greatly, O Daugher of Zion.
    Disc 9 side (A) includes O Thou that Tellest (conc.). Side (B) includes (A) There Were Shepherds; And Lo, the Angel of the Lord; And the Angel Said; And Suddenly (B) Glory to God.
    Disc 10 side (A) includes For Behold, Darkness Shall Cover the Earth. Side (B) includes Pastoral Symphony.
    Disc 11 side (A) includes The People that Walked in Darkness. Side (B) includes For Unto Us a Child is Born. The album also includes program notes and text inside cover.
  - The Messiah (Record CAS CLA 0043)
    This album consists of 10 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes And With His Stripes. Side (B) includes Amen.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes All We Like Sheep. Side (B) includes Worthy is the Lamb.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes (A) All They That See Him (B) He Trusted in God. Side (B) includes (A) If God Be For Us (conc.) (B) Let All the Angels of God.
    Disc 4 side (A) includes (A) Thy Rebuke Hath Broken His Heart (B) Behold and See. Side (B) includes If God Be For Us (Part 1).
    Disc 5 side (A) includes (A) But He Was Cut Off (B) But Thou Didst Not Leave. Side (B) includes (A) Then Shalle Be Brought to Pass (B) But Thanks Be to God.
    Disc 6 side (A) includes Lift Up Your Heads. Side (B) includes The Trumpet Shall Sound (conc.).
    Disc 7 side (A) includes Thou Art Gone Up on High. Side (B) includes (A) Since By Man Came Death (B) Behold I Tell You a Mystery (C) The Trumpet Shall Sound (Part 1).
    Disc 8 side (A) includes (A) The Lord Gave the Word (B) How Beautiful are the Feet of Them. Side (B) includes I Know that My Redeemer Liveth (conc.).
    Disc 9 side (A) includes (A) Their Sound is Gone Out (B) Why Do the Nations. Side (B) includes I Know that My Redeemer Liveth (Part 1).
    Disc 10 side (A) includes (A) Let Us Break Their Bonds Asunder (B) He that Dwelleth in Heaven (C) Thou Shalt Break Them. Side (B) includes Hallelujah!
  - The Haydn Quartet Society-Volume 7. Haydn Quartets: Op. 3, No. 4; Op. 64, No. 3; Op. 50, No. 6; Op. 74, No. 1. A Victor Musical Masterpiece (Record CAS CLA 0044)
    This album consists of 7 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes 1. Allegro. Side (B) includes 2. Adagio-Presto.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes 2. Poco adagio. Side (B) includes 1. Allegro moderato.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes 3. Menuetto (Allegretto) and Trio. Side (B) includes 4. Finale (Allegro con spirito).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes 4. Finale (Allegro con spirito). Side (B) includes 3. Menuetto (Allegretto) and Trio.
    Disc 5 side (A) includes 1. Allegro Moderato. Side (B) includes 2. Adagio.
    Disc 6 side (A) includes 2. Andantino grazioso. Side (B) includes 1. Vivace assai.
    Disc 7 side (A) includes 3. Menuetto (Allegretto) and Trio. Side (B) includes 4. Finale (Vivace).
  - Victor Herbert Beloved American Composer: A collection of Victor Herbert's Music on New Orthophonic Victrola Records (Record CAS CLA 0045)
    This album consists of 3 discs with 2 sides each. Dsic 1 side (A) includes Ah! Sweet Mystery of Life (The Dream Melody). Side (B) includes (A) I'm Faling in Love With Someone (B) Italian Street Song.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes Badinage. Side (B) includes (A) Aire de Ballet (B) Al Fresco.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes Badinage. Side (B) includes (A) Aire de Ballet (B) Al Fresco. The album is missing several records from set. Album cover is damaged. The last disc in the album is stored in album sleeve of Victor Herbert Beloved American Composer.
  - Hindemith Sonata No. 3 (1939) For Viola and Piano (Record CAS CLA 0046)
    This album consists of 4 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes 1. Breit mit Kraft (Part 1). Side (B) includes Laura y Georgina.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes 1. Breit mit Kraft (conc.). Side (B) includes 4. Theme with two variations (conc.).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes 2. Sehr lebhaft (Part 1). Side (B) includes 4. Theme with two variations (Part 1).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes 2. Sehr lebhaft (conc.). Side (B) includes 3. Phantasie. Album also includes program notes by V[einus], A.
  - Ibert Escales (ports of call) (Record CAS CLA 0047)
    This album consists of 2 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes 1. Rome-Palermo (Part 1). Side (B) includes 3. Valencia (conc.).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes (A) 1. Rome-Palermo (conc.) (B) 2. Tunis-Nefta. Side (B) includes 3. Valencia (Part 1). Album also includes program notes by Hall, David inside cover.
  - Khathaturian: Concerto for Piano and Orchestra. William Kapell, pianist with Boston Symphony Orchestra; Serge Koussevetzky, conductor (Record CAS CLA 0048)
    This album consists of 4 discs wuth 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes Concerto for Piano and Orchestra (1936) First Movement: Allegro ma non troppo e maestoso (Part 1). Side (B) includes Concerto for Piano and Orchestra (1936) Third Movement: Allegro brillante (conclusion).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes Concerto for Piano and Orchestra (1936) First Movement: Allegro ma non troppo e maestoso (Part 2). Side (B) includes Concerto for Piano and Orchestra (1936) Third Movement: Allegro brillante (Part 1).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes Concerto for Piano and Orchestra (1936) First Movement: Allegro ma non troppo e maestoso (Part 3). Side (B) includes Concerto for Piano and Orchestra (1936) Second Movement: Andante con anima (Concluded).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes Concerto for Piano and Orchestra (1936) First Movement: Allegro ma non troppo e maestoso (concluded). Side (B) includes Concerto for Piano and Orchestra (1936) Second Movement: Andante con anima (Part 1). Album is duplicate of John Harvith 0751-0758. Short introductory note by Hall, David.
  - Concerto in F Minor, Op. 3, 1948 (Record CAS CLA 0049)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes 2. Andante (Part 1). Side (B) includes 2. Andante (conc.). Original sleeve is in new sleeve.
  - Fritz Kreisler Program (Record CAS CLA 0050)
    This album consists of 3 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes The Old Refrain. Side (B) includes Miniature Viennese Waltz.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes Rondino on a Theme by Beethoven. Side (B) includes Midnight Bells.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes Londonberry Air. Side (B) includes Hungarian Rondo. This album also includes program notes inside cover.
  - Kirsten, Dorothy (soprano); Merrill, Robert (baritone); Morel, Jean Paul (conductor) and the RCA Victor Orchestra/ Journet, Marcel (bass) with orchestra; (A) Mort de Thais (B) Te Souvient--Il du lumineux voyage; In quelle trine Morbide; Philémon et Baucis; Les Huguenots: Act I (Record CAS CLA 0051)
    This album consists of 2 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes (A) Mort de Thais (B) Te Souvient--Il du lumineux voyage. Side (B) includes In quelle trine Morbide.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes Au Bruit Lourd des Marteaux. Side (B) includes Piff! Paff! This album was recorded in 1910. Original sleeve is in new sleeve.
  - Louise Homer sings Nobil Signors, Saluta! from Meyerbeer's opera Les Huguenots (recorded in 1905) and Die Allmacht by Schubert (recorded in 1909), 1947 (Record CAS CLA 0052)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Nobil Signors, Saluta! Side (B) includes Die Allmacht. This album is in a gold cover.
  - Pol Plancon sings Invocation from Mozart's Opera The Magic Flute and Le Lazzarone by Ferrari/Le Flibustier by Georges, 1947 (Record CAS CLA 0053)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Invocation. Side (B) includes (A) Le Lazzarone (B) Le Flibustier. The album is in a gold cover and was recorded in 1905.
  - Don Giovanni: Act I (Record CAS CLA 0054)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Both sides include Madamina, il cataloga. The record is chipped.
  - Don Giovanni: Act II, 1945 (Record CAS CLA 0055)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 1 side. The disc includes Il mio tesoro intanto andate a consolar!
  - Tetrazzini, Luisa (soprano) with orchestra; The Marriage of Figaro: Act II; Mignon: Act II (Record CAS CLA 0056)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) incudes Voi che sapete? Side (B) includes Io son Titania. Original sleeve is in new sleeve.
  - Mozart Symphony No. 40, in G Minor (K. 550) (Record CAS CLA 0057)
    This album consists of 3 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes I. Allegro molto. Side (B) includes II. Andante (conc.).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes I. Allegro Molto (conc.). Side (B) includes III. Menuetto: Allegro and Trio.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes II. Andante (beg.). Side (B) includes IV. Finale: Allegro assai. Program notes by Veinus, A. included in booklet.
  - Gaîté Parisienne: Music by Jacques Offenbach, Orchestrated by Manuel Rosenthal, As Presented by Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo (Record CAS CLA 0058)
    This album consists of 4 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes Gaîté Parisienne (ballet) (Part 1). Side (B) includes Gaîté Parisienne (ballet) (Part 8). Disc 2 side (A) includes Gaîté Parisienne (ballet) (Part 2). Side (B) includes Gaîté Parisienne (ballet) (Part 7).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes Gaîté Parisienne (ballet) (Part 3). Side (B) includes Gaîté Parisienne (ballet) (Part 6).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes Gaîté Parisienne (ballet) (Part 4). Side (B) includes Gaîté Parisienne (ballet) (Part 5). This album also includes program notes by Hall, David inside cover.
  - La Gioconda: Act III (Record CAS CLA 0059)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Dance of the Hours-Part 1. Side (B) includes Dance of the Hours-Part 2.
  - John McCormack and G. Mario Sammargo sing Ah, Mimi, tu più non torni from Puccini's Opera La Bohême (recorded in 1910) and Lucrezia Bori and John McCormack sing Parigi, O cara from Verdi's Opera La Traviata (recorded in 1914), 1947 (Record CAS CLA 0060)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Ah, Mimi, tu più non torni. Side (B) includes Parigi, O cara. The album is in a gold cover.
  - Emmy Destinn sings Un bel di vedremo from Puccini's opera Madama Butterfly (recorded in 1908) and Suicidio, in questi fieiri momenti from Ponchielli's opera La Gioconda (recorded in 1914), 1947 (Record CAS CLA 0061)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Un bel di vedremo. Side (B) includes Suicido, in questi fieri momenti. This album is in a gold cover.
  - Highlights from Puccini's Madame Butterfly (Record CAS CLA 0062)
    This album consists of 3 disc with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes Love Duet (Part 1): Stolta paura, l'amor (Fear no, my dearest, for love). Side (B) includes Addio (Farewell).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes Love Duet (conc.): Dicon cho'oltre mare (They say that in your country). Side (B) includes Flower Duet (conc.): Spoglia è l'orto (Not a flow'r left).
    Disc 3 includes Un Bel Di, Vedremo (One fine day…). Side (B) includes Flower Duet (Part 1): Spoglia è l'orto (Not a flow'r left). This album also includes program notes inside album cover.
  - Puccini La Tosca: Volume 1 (Record CAS CLA 0063)
    This album consists of 7 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes Ah! Finalmente. Side (B) includes Son Pronto.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes Sante Ampolle!. Side (B) includes Amaro sol per te.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes Ma con quei cani. Side (B) includes Tu? Di tua man l'uccidesti?
    Disc 4 side (A) includes Ora stammi a sentir. Side (B) includes E lucevan le stelle.
    Disc 5 side (A) includes Or lasciami al lavoro. Side (B) includes Murio Cavaradossi? a voi.
    Disc 6 side (A) includes Mia gelosa. Side (B) includes Prelude, Act 3 (L'alba).
    Disc 7 side (A) includes E buona la mia Tosca. Side (B) includes Canzone del pastore. This album is missing volume 2.
  - RACHMANINOFF: Concerto No. 4 In G Minor. Sergi Rachmaninoff with The Philadelphia Orchestra, Eugene Ormandy, Conductor (Record CAS CLA 0064)
    This album consists of 4 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes Concerto No. 4, In G Minor, Op. 40 - First Movement: Allegro vivace (Part 1). Side (B) includes Concerto No. 4, In G Minor, Op. 40 - Third Movement: Allegro vivace (concluded).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes Concerto No. 4, In G Minor, Op. 40 - First Movement: Allegro vivace (Part 2). Side (B) includes Concerto No. 4, In G Minor, Op. 40 - Third Movement: Allegro vivace (Part 2).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes Concerto No. 4, In G Minor, Op. 40 - First Movement: Allegro vivace (concluded). Side (B) includes Concerto No. 4, In G Minor, Op. 40 - Third Movement: Allegro vivace (Part 1).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes Concerto No. 4, In G Minor, Op. 40 - Second Movement: Largo (Part 1). Side (B) includes Concerto No. 4, In G Minor, Op. 40 - Second Movement: Largo (concluded). Album also includes a brief introductory note. Album set duplicates John Harvith 0864-0871.
  - Victor Showpiece: Daphnis et Chloé Suite No. II by Maurice Ravel (Record CAS CLA 0065)
    This album consists of 2 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 sid e(A) includes 1. Lever du jour (Daybreak). Side (B) includes 3. Danse Générale (General Dance).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes 2. Pantomime (Part 1). Side (B) includes 2. Pantomime (conc.). This album also includes program notes inside cover. Disc 1 is chipped and the album cover is loose.
  - Bernstein Plays Ravel: Ravel Concerto for Piano and Orchestra (Record CAS CLA 0066)
    This album consists of 3 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes First Movement: Allegramente (Part 1). Side (B) includes (A) 4. For Paul Bowles (B) 5. In Memoriam Nathalie Koussevitzsky.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes First Movement: Andante: Tempo Primo (concluded). Side (B) includes Third Movement: Presto.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes Second Movement: Adagio assai (Part 1). Side (B) includes Second Movement: Adagio assai (concluded). Album is duplicate of John Harvith 2246-2251. Set includes two short works by Bernstein.
  - Music of the Renaissance: Max Meili, Tenor (Record CAS CLA 0067)
    This album consists of 3 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes (A) Triste estaba el Rey David (B) De la sangra de tus nobles. Side (B) includes (A) Señora, si te olvidaré (B) Soneto: Al Monte Sale.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes Durandarte. Side (B) includes (A) Perdida tengo la color (B) La Mañana de San Juan.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes (A) Come, Deep Sleep (B) Come Again. Side (B) includes (A) Con Lagrime e Sospir (B) It Was a Lover. This album also includes program notes inside cover.
  - The Pines…The Fountains of Rome: Toscanini and the NBC Symphony Orchestra (Record CAS CLA 0068)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes (A) The Pines of the Villa Borghese (B) The Pines Near a Catacomb (C) The Pines of the Janiculum (D) The Pines of the Appian Way. Side (B) includes (A) The Fountain of Valle Giulia at Dawn (B) The Triton Fountain at Morn (C) The Fountain of Trevi at Mid-day (D) The Villa Medici Fountain at Sunset. These discs are LPs. Booklet includes notes on music and on Rome by Sheean, Vincent, as well as photos of Rome.
  - Scheherazade-Symphonic Suite, Op. 35 (Record CAS CLA 0069)
    This album consists of 6 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes 1st Mov.: The Sea and the Vessel of Sinbad. Side (B) includes 4th Mov.: The Vessel is Wrecked (conc.).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes 1st Mov.: The Sea and the Vessel of Sinbad (cont.). Side (B) includes 4th Mov.: Festival at Bagdad (conc.); The Sea.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes 1st Mov.: The Sea and the Vessel of Sinbad (conc.). Side (B) includes 4th Mov.: Festival at Bagdad.
    Disc 4 side (A) includes 2nd Mov.: The Tale of the Prince Kalendar. Side (B) includes 3rd Mov.: The Young Prince and the Young Princess (conc.).
    Disc 5 side (A) includes 2nd Mov.: The Tale of the Prince Kalendar (cont.). Side (B) includes 3rd Mov.: The Young Prince and the Young Princess (cont.).
    Disc 6 side (A) includes 2nd Mov.: The Tale of the Prince Kalendar (conc.). Side (B) includes 3rd Mov.: The Young Prince and the Young Princess. This album also includes booklet with program notes.
  - Rossini Overtures (Record CAS CLA 0070)
    This album consists of 4 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes The Barber of Seville: Overture (Part 1). Side (B) includes Passo a sie (Dance).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes The Barber of Seville: Overture (conc.). Side (B) includes Il Signor Bruschino: Overture.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes La Gazza Ladra: Overture. Side (B) includes La Cenerentola: Overture (conc.).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes La Gazza Ladra: Overture (conc.). Side (B) includes La Cenerentola: Overture (Part 1). This album also includes program notes on inside of album cover.
  - Schubert Symphony No. 5 in B-Flat (Record CAS CLA 0071)
    This album consists of 3 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes 1. Allegro. Side (B) includes 4. Allegro Vivace.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes 2. Andante con moto (Part 1). Side (B) includes 3. Menuetto.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes 2. Andante con moto (Part 2). Side (B) includes 2. Andante con moto (conc.). This album also includes program notes by Hall, David inside cover.
  - Schumann "Rhenish" Symphony, No. 3 in E-Flat, Op. 97 (Record CAS CLA 0072)